<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Snappysnaps on backshots.photo</title>
    <link>https://backshots.photo/tags/snappysnaps/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Snappysnaps on backshots.photo</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 13:56:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://backshots.photo/tags/snappysnaps/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Nikon F100 with FPP Redscale</title>
      <link>https://backshots.photo/film/nikon-f100-fpp-redscale/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 13:56:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://backshots.photo/film/nikon-f100-fpp-redscale/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Redscale&#34;&gt;Redscale&lt;/a&gt; is an interesting technique to me as it&amp;rsquo;s just the sort of thing that someone would do by accident somehow and then discover &amp;ldquo;oh, this is good actually.&amp;rdquo; Combined with the fact that it&amp;rsquo;s simply using something incorrectly (exposing film through the base of the film stock so that light hits the red-sensitive layers first), it has just the level of ingenuity and slapshod hackery to make me love it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nikon F100 with Kodak Ultramax 400</title>
      <link>https://backshots.photo/film/nikon-f100-ultramax/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 13:56:53 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://backshots.photo/film/nikon-f100-ultramax/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Kodak films have never been particularly exciting to me: they’ve always felt a little staid and understated in their rendition of colour. With something like a ten year gap since I last really shot film, the colour film options available have somewhat reduced: outside of the more exotic cinema 35mm films and other ‘boutique’ films, there are only really a handful of options that are likely be available in more common high-street settings. With that in mind, I’d decided to cast aside my prejudice and give it a go.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Petri 7s &#43; Harman  Phoenix 200</title>
      <link>https://backshots.photo/film/petri-phoenix/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 13:56:53 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://backshots.photo/film/petri-phoenix/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m a sucker for anything I think I can fix. Whether this is people, the annoying drip from the pipe in a family member&amp;rsquo;s kitchen or a camera that someone else has deemed irreparable. The latter reared its head when I was sixteen, with a Petri 7s that I bought from eBay for what was probably £15 (£24.40 in 2024 prices, adjusted for inflation). The leaf blades of the shutter were completely seized and covered in what could only be fairly described as &amp;ldquo;gunk&amp;rdquo; and I had a copy of the service manual. A copy of the service manual and absolutely no finesse with my hands was not sufficient to salvage the camera.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
